all right everybody Wow
好的，大家哇
my brain brain is a on fire
我的大脑大脑着火了
welcome are we this is the last day
欢迎光临，这是最后一天
right I I wish but isn't it wait there's
正确的II愿望，但是不是吗？
tomorrow too their stuff is their stuff
明天也是他们的东西
tomorrow
明天
really yeah oh I just stopped working
真的，是的，我刚停止工作
again what day is today Wednesday night
今天星期三晚上又是星期几
or Tuesday Tuesday Wednesday right so
还是星期二星期二星期三
tomorrow's Thursday so there is content
明天的星期四有内容
tomorrow okay well got nothing move on
明天好吧，什么也没动
so uh good morning how you can join the
嗯，早上好，你怎么可以加入
show so far don't here boo oh you what
显示到目前为止，不要在这里嘘哦，你怎么了
oh cool yeah I love it too some some
哦，是的，我太喜欢了
good talks you don't get content wearing
好话不让你感到满足
cool things right oh it's been crazy
很酷的东西，哦，这太疯狂了
I thought the rush leading up to this
我以为这导致了匆忙
event was crazy cuz it's always just a
事件太疯狂了，因为它总是
thousand things right before we go what
一千种东西就在我们走之前
right before we get here but now it's
就在我们到达这里之前，但是现在
just been it's even more crazy here well
只是在这里变得更加疯狂
anyway thanks for joining us who are you
无论如何，感谢您加入我们的行列
my name is Adam Coblentz I'm a product
我的名字是亚当·科布伦茨我是产品
manager at zero turn around I used to be
经理在零转弯我曾经是
a enterprise software engineer and then
企业软件工程师，然后
I left to a startup and what came up
我离开一家初创公司，结果
what does enterprise mean oh well it
企业是什么意思
used to mean writing custom frameworks
过去是指编写自定义框架
on top of java ee in spring yeah which
在春季的Java EE上面
was horrifying but that left for a
令人恐惧，但留下了
start-up I gave up all my awesome
创业我放弃了我所有的真棒
benefits but I'm much happier and if the
好处，但我要快乐得多，如果
bean talked to awesome people like you
豆跟像你这样的真棒人聊天
guys and Josh well yeah see oh you are
伙计们和乔希（Josh）很好，是的，哦，你是
um hi I'm Josh I uh who are you supposed
嗯，我是乔希，你应该是谁
to say hi I'm whatever
说你好我是什么
time okay so I can Josh I'm just falling
时间还可以，所以我可以乔希，我只是跌倒了
on the well I'm a spring developer
在井上，我是一名春季开发人员
advocate I'm on the Twitter's so if
提倡我在Twitter上，所以如果
you're on the Twitter's at at Starbucks
您在星巴克的Twitter上
man please don't hesitate to you know
男人，请不要犹豫
say hi it's kind of cool it's the new IR
说嗨，这很酷，是新的IR
C so we're there loud and proud okay
C，所以我们在那里喧闹而自豪
next we're gonna talk and of course I
接下来我们要谈，当然我
work at pivotal and a pivotal pivotal we
在关键和关键枢纽工作
care about going as quickly and safely
关心尽快安全地走
as possible we have in spring a very
尽可能在春季
unique opportunity that there's actually
实际上有独特的机会
about a more than a decade's worth of
大约十多年的价值
apps out there a lot of these apps tend
应用程序很多，这些应用程序往往
to be you know if they were written with
要知道它们是否与
spring boot and within the word micro
spring boot 和微字内
services model in mind hopefully they're
希望他们记住服务模型
very svelte and you know quick to to
很苗条，你知道很快
iterate with but of course there's a lot
与迭代，但当然有很多
of applications that were developed a
已开发的应用程序
top large application servers these
这些大型顶级应用服务器
kinds of environments etc and so they
各种环境等，所以他们
can be a little bit slower to to iterate
迭代可能会有点慢
with and of course now we also have this
与当然，现在我们也有这个
new destination for applications which
应用程序的新目的地
is the cloud and sometimes you just
是云，有时你只是
absolutely want to be able to run your
绝对希望能够运行您的
apps and and make changes as you're
应用程序，并根据需要进行更改
developing on the cloud and that can be
在云上发展，这可能是
a little slow as well compared to just
与刚才相比，也有点慢
restarting in ID that is one of the
以以下方式之一重新启动ID：
things that we found is pretty cool as
我们发现的东西很酷
developers you know like when the karoku
你知道的开发者，当karoku
started right it was like I cannot have
正确的开始就像我不能
a thing in the cloud that I quickly but
云里的东西，我很快但是
I have no mechanism to get things there
我没有办法把东西拿到那里
in a way I understand and the clouds
以我理解的方式和云
kind of cool but my laptops while the
有点酷，但我的笔记本电脑虽然
power is and it was kind of new figuring
力量是一种新的象征
out yeah now we have an awesome
没关系，现在我们有一个很棒的
stuff like that foundry which integrates
像铸造厂这样的东西
with yeah terrible so we're gonna talk
是的，太可怕了，我们要谈谈
about sort of what it means to move or
关于移动意味着什么
move through development with a with J
与J一起进行开发
rebel first we're gonna take a look at
首先造反，我们来看看
what J Robo actually is how would even
J Robo实际上是什至
know what J verbally is okay so for the
知道J的口头上还可以
most of you this won't be so Gerald's
你们大多数人不会是杰拉德的
made by zero turnaround we make
通过零周转产生
revolutionary developer tools the idea
革命性的开发人员使用该工具
is that I used to have a 16-minute
是我过去有16分钟的时间
redeploy on my yeah see you're laughing
重新部署我，是的，看到你在笑
you
您
didn't even view have a yeah 15 minute
甚至都没看15分钟
redeploy yeah yeah so like you met you
重新部署是的，所以就像你遇见你
hit save and you've spent 30 minutes
点击保存，您已经花了30分钟
doing nothing right and of course but
无所作为，当然，但是
you the imagine doesn't know that your
你想象中的不知道你的
manager does not know you do nothing
经理不知道你什么都不做
right so like that xkcd cartoon what do
对，所以像那xkcd卡通做什么
you have compiling okay carry on I think
你已经编译好了，继续吧，我想
I went to Starbucks more when I was
我那时去星巴克的时间更多
working on that project than any other
在那个项目上胜过其他任何人
time in my life like not in college
我一生中的时光就像不在大学里
so we think the joke is it's a
所以我们认为这个笑话是
bacon-wrapped Ferrari right cuz like
培根包裹的法拉利车，因为像
what's awesome Bacon's awesome Ferraris
培根棒极了的法拉利车
are awesome I want to be here Friday so
太棒了，我想星期五在这里，所以
we currently have about 65,000 users
我们目前有大约65,000个用户
then that also includes people who use
那也包括那些使用
our free version for you know students
我们为您认识的学生提供的免费版本
and non-commercial for example and the
和非商业性的
idea is that you don't have to redeploy
想法是您不必重新部署
your application anymore like you you
您的应用程序不再像您一样
build it you deploy it you hit save in
构建它，部署它，然后点击保存
eclipse you hit you know you hit ctrl F
蚀你击中你知道你击中ctrl F
and I in and IntelliJ and refreshing
和我在和IntelliJ和刷新
your browser and your code just kind of
您的浏览器和您的代码只是
works the way you want to and the idea
按照您想要的方式和想法工作
is like you know everyone you know heard
就像你认识每个认识的人
of hot-swap right it's built on the JVM
基于JVM构建的热插拔功能
you go into the debugger and you can
您进入调试器，您可以
change a method body maybe you can use
改变方法的身体也许你可以使用
hot deploy for example and eventually
例如热部署，最终
run out of MJ and leaky class loaders
用完MJ和泄漏类加载器
for example and you'll get that message
例如，您会收到该消息
that message that no one really
那个消息，没有人真的
understands why they're getting it in
了解为什么他们要加入
STS and Eclipse like you know unable to
就像您知道的STS和Eclipse无法
make this change you know we to
做出更改，您知道我们要
republish your application now right and
立即重新发布您的应用程序，然后
that's it's it's like thanks this is
就是这样，谢谢
like the blue screen of death for a
就像死亡的蓝屏
developer like I don't understand what
像我这样的开发人员不明白
this is saying to me and my ID basically
这是对我说的，我的身份证基本上
what happens is like when you're making
当你做的时候会发生什么
changes it's hot deploy for example
例如更改它的热部署
you're actually you know creating new
实际上，您知道创建新的
class loaders and the other ones don't
类加载器，其他则不
get garbage bucket properly and you lose
正确得到垃圾桶，你会输
state and all kinds of awful terrible
状态和各种可怕的
things like that so if you have a
这样的事情，所以如果你有一个
stateful application you know you might
有状态的应用程序，您知道您可能会
have to recreate this very long
必须重新创建很长时间
complicated workflow but you don't lose
复杂的工作流程，但您不会输
any of that with terrible you can also
任何可怕的你也可以
change resource files and we're also
更改资源文件，我们也
here because we have integration like
在这里，因为我们有像
with spring and like a hundred other
春天和其他一百个
frameworks
构架
if you have some poor sucker who has to
如果你有一些可怜的吸盘谁必须
use Java EE I mix Josh so sad like look
使用Java EE我将Josh混合在一起，让它看起来很难过
at him sad panda yeah but if you have
对他难过的熊猫是的，但如果你有
someone who is stuck using one of those
被困其中之一的人
things or using spring with some of the
东西或使用弹簧与一些
new awesome stuff also available to you
新的很棒的东西也可以给你
it should all kind of work so the idea
它应该进行所有工作，所以这个主意
is that you know you may not realize how
是你知道你可能没有意识到
much time you actually like spending
你实际上很喜欢花费时间
waiting for your tooling right we
等待您的工具对我们
actually did this we had this huge
实际上做到了，我们有这么大
experiment we have a part of our company
实验我们是我们公司的一部分
is called rebel labs and what we do
被称为反叛实验室，我们做什么
there is we actually violently create
我们实际上是在激烈地创造
reports we create content you know
报告我们创建您知道的内容
there's just generally interesting to
总的来说有趣
people and so we do this huge survey
人们，所以我们进行了这项庞大的调查
about 2,000 people and we also get more
大约2,000人，而且我们还会得到更多
feedback more at JavaOne and we ask
在JavaOne上获得更多反馈，我们问
people you know how often do you make
你认识的人你多久做一次
changes to your app and development are
您的应用程序和开发的变化是
you constantly iterating is it very
你不断地迭代是非常
carefully planned you know how long is
精心计划，你知道要多久
it take you to make a change and wait
你需要做出改变并等待
for your app to build for example and
以您的应用为例
the numbers are actually kind of absurd
这些数字实际上是荒谬的
we found that the average developer
我们发现一般的开发人员
spends about a full work month a year
一年大约花一个完整的工作
waiting for redeploys and I mean just
等待重新部署，我的意思是
think about like what that means to you
想想这对你意味着什么
like you are sitting there trying to get
就像你坐在那里试图获得
your work done trying to hit you know
你的工作试图打你知道
your goal for the sprint and you're
您对冲刺的目标，
working more and more overtime because
加班越来越多，因为
you can't get your stuff done you know
你知道你做不完的事
and you're working more and more you're
而且你工作越来越多
not going home on time I had a problem
我不能按时回家有问题
where I had you know when I had the 16
当我16岁时，我知道你在哪里
minute redeploy where I actually had to
分钟的重新部署，我实际上不得不
deliver this thing that was even more
提供的东西甚至更多
complicated and I didn't go home before
很复杂，我以前没回家
10:30 any night that week before the end
结束前一周的晚上10:30
of the sprint because they're just
冲刺的原因，因为它们只是
trying to get this thing done so we want
试图把事情做好，所以我们想要
to make you able to go home to your
使您能够回家
families right
家庭权利
so you get less stressed out your
这样可以减轻您的压力
managers happy because you're getting
经理很高兴，因为你越来越
your Sprint's done you know you're
你的Sprint完成了，你知道你是
fearfully running better good sheer
可怕地运行更好的纯粹
tyranny of will yeah exactly yeah
是的暴政是的，是的
we actually had one of our customers of
我们实际上有我们的客户之一
the case study that they were able to do
他们能够做的案例研究
percent more work in the same amount of
相同数量的工作量增加了百分之
time because they had to like j-wahl
时间，因为他们必须喜欢j-wahl
which is cool because you think about
这很酷，因为您考虑
how much time your she's spending like
你花了多少时间像
they were actually able to spend more
他们实际上有能力花更多钱
time planning out the iteration and got
时间计划迭代并得到
more more reliable time metrics for how
更可靠的时间指标
long you can actually like produce code
只要您实际上可以喜欢产生代码
which is always the one the hardest
永远是最难的
things right cuz you're you know your
正确的事情，因为你是你知道你的
manager asks you how long will take you
经理问你要花多长时间
to do this this feature and you you're
为此功能，您
guessing right it's kind of like based
猜对了，有点像基于
on your experience and well the first
根据您的经验，第一个
time to run it down Jenny yeah exactly
是时候把它用完了珍妮是的
you know never mind that edge case I
你知道没关系我这种情况
found that's gonna take me three days to
发现那要花我三天时间
fix right but I see idea
解决正确，但我明白了主意
so also regardless of how complex your
所以不管你有多复杂
app is right if you have like a one
如果您喜欢一个应用程序，那么它是正确的
class you know spring mood app or you
您知道春季心情应用程序还是您上课
have a thirty module huge gigantic thing
有三十个模块的巨大东西
that runs some bank that's okay you can
可以经营一些银行，你可以
work with you know jars inside of wars
与您合作知道战争中的罐子
inside of ears if you use those that's
如果您使用的是耳朵内部
all fine no problem
一切都没问题
can I just show of hands so again we're
我可以举手吗，所以我们再次
hoping that modern applications are
希望现代应用程序能够
small spelled micro services but of
小型拼写微服务，但
course that's a front you know to
当然这是你知道的前沿
progression and so of course not
进展，所以当然不是
not everything is there yet so how many
不是所有的东西都那么多
of you are are using let's see WebSphere
你们正在使用，让我们看看WebSphere
Justin you're among friends
贾斯汀，你在朋友当中
no one's judging we all tried it once in
没有人判断我们都尝试过一次
college now those of you using WebSphere
现在就开始使用WebSphere的那些人
how many of you using Liberty versus
你们当中有多少人使用Liberty与
full profile you're starting to okay so
完整资料，您现在可以了，所以
mostly it's it's full profile like the
主要是它的完整资料，例如
actual wbf with Waze add me on yeah well
实际与Waze的wbf将我加入了
okay okay so and then what about be a
好的，好的，然后再成为一个
Sun Oracle WebLogic anybody know one one
Sun Oracle WebLogic谁都知道一个
okay cool we have three three I don't
好的，很酷，我们有三个三个
count too good no okay
计数太好了不好
what about one of the other ones I've
那我有一个其他的呢
got oh yeah I'm using Tomcat and he's
哦，是的，我正在使用Tomcat，而他
not good that's a thing I've had I've
不好，那是我曾经拥有过的东西
heard stories no what about wildfly neh
没听过有关野蝇的故事吗
JBoss is a couple okay
JBoss没事
okay wait there's more WebLogic than
好的，还有更多的WebLogic
wildfly know they were wasn't the same
野蝇知道他们不一样
people yeah no yes yeah okay honey it's
人是的，不是，是的，亲爱的，这是
up to you right there's like jetty right
取决于你，就像码头一样
what resident anyways jetty or resin
无论如何居民码头或树脂
jetty cool jetty resin resin jetty okay
码头凉码头树脂树脂码头可以
cool resin do you doesn't really
很酷的树脂，你不是真的吗
remember risen how about how about OSGi
记得复活OSGi怎么样
okay oh that's GI okay couple more
好的，那是GI好的，还有更多
WebLogic than OSGi yeah talk about it
WebLogic胜过OSGi呀
anyway
无论如何
yeah I'm just curious where people are
是的，我很好奇人们在哪里
yeah yeah that's that's fine you know I
是的，那很好，你知道我
actually had someone come and talk to me
其实有人来跟我说话
and they currently are on like a super
他们现在像超级
old like Java EE 6 and like WebLogic
像Java EE 6和WebLogic一样古老
thing and they're here because they want
的东西，他们在这里，因为他们想要
to migrate to booth I'm the fan I know
迁移到展位我是我认识的粉丝
right that's an awesome idea
对，这是一个很棒的主意
so the ado is that I'll see how this
所以说白了，我会看看
actually looks on that's really small
实际上看起来很小
yeah can you read that it is adding
是的你能读到它正在添加
removing oh yeah I'm gonna try to make
删除哦，是的，我要尝试
this like wow let's see how this works
像哇，让我们看看它是如何工作的
this is this is like a kinda silly thing
这就像种愚蠢的事情
see yeah this is the important thing
看，这是重要的
like that yeah of course I just do so
就是这样，我当然会这样做
much stuff so basically the idea is that
很多东西，所以基本上这个想法是
just about any kind of like Java change
几乎任何类似Java的更改
you want to make to your application or
您想制作您的应用程序或
all so cool groovy you know Scala
一切都很酷，您知道Scala
they'll also work doesn't work but does
他们也会工作不起作用，但是可以
it work on Delavan
它在Delavan上工作
it does actually oh we have early access
确实有哦，我们可以尽早使用
for Java for Android there you go
适用于Android的Java
that's pretty clear we're send devices
很明显，我们正在发送设备
as well which is another place where it
以及在另一个地方
just takes an age right like I don't
只是像我这样的年龄
understand exactly how I think I do I
完全了解我的想法
don't understand how the iOS simulator
不明白iOS模拟器如何
can be blazing fast but an Android takes
可以快速发展，但Android需要
like a week yeah
像一个星期
so that one get all shifted but this is
这样一个人全都变了，但这是
the important stuff you do things no but
您要做的重要事情就是
yeah so basically the idea is like if
是的，所以基本上这个想法是
you want you one thing about from the
你想从中得到一件事
Android users right the idea is pushing
Android用户正确的想法正在推动
a new version of your application to a
您的应用程序的新版本
device or the simulator is the same as
设备或模拟器与
basically redeploying application on App
基本上在App上重新部署应用程序
server right
服务器权限
and so we as of two weeks ago have an
因此，截至两周前，
early access type thing that works
抢先体验式的东西
pretty awesome actually with with
真的很棒
Android so if you do use that you know
Android，因此，如果您使用它，就会知道
give it a go right on yeah
继续吧
so cool and we're here because we work
太酷了，我们在这里，因为我们在工作
with you know Spring Grails Ruby
和你知道Spring Grails Ruby
language boot cloud foundry and whereas
语言引导云代工厂，而
you're going to show you some of this
您将向您展示一些
stuff um
东西
actually we could show you girls to mmm
其实我们可以告诉你女孩mmmm
we're gonna focus on you have time do
我们会专注于您有时间
you a demo for that I couldn't actually
你一个我实际上无法演示的演示
scaffold an app from scratch with zero
从零开始搭建一个应用
before yeah okay well might be a weren't
没错，好吧可能不是
doing that too yeah yeah we have a
也是那样，是的，我们有一个
problem I'm just gonna be very honest
问题，我只是说实话
with you yeah we tried every which way
是的，我们与您一起尝试了所有方法
to get this talk to go for an hour and a
使这个演讲进行一个小时又一个
half but we're so tarnishing there's no
一半，但我们是如此失去光泽
like there's no restart so it it doesn't
就像没有重启，所以它不会
go for an hour and a half and that's the
一个半小时，那就是
problem so we may actually let out a
问题，所以我们实际上可能会让
little bit early for lunch I know you're
早点吃午饭我知道你是
disappointed but this is kind of where
失望，但这是一个地方
we are right yeah we basically were able
是的，是的，我们基本上能够
to turn a talk that usually takes an
开个通常需要
hour and a half and make it like a lot
一个半小时，使它像很多
less we're trying to make it longer now
少一点，我们现在要延长它的时间
we're making it longer someone help Adam
我们让某人帮助亚当的时间更长
work on Chinese no right we're adding
不行，我们要加中文
value okay right so we're gonna just
值好吧，所以我们要
throw everything and see what you know
扔东西，看看你知道什么
good picture so what's cool is like the
好图片，所以很酷，就像
reason I was asking about the other
我问另一个的原因
stuff right is because obviously you use
正确的事情是因为显然您使用
spring because you're here and that's
春天，因为你在这里，那是
awesome but you don't work in a you know
很棒，但是你不会在一个你知道的地方工作
in a closed silo you exist in a team you
在封闭的筒仓中，您存在于团队中
know just in some large corporation
只是在某个大公司中知道
possibly and there's other stuff going
可能还有其他的东西
on all right so while you may be working
好的，所以当您可能正在工作时
in some awesome spring boo agile team
在一些很棒的春季boo敏捷团队中
you might have to deal with other stuff
你可能不得不处理其他东西
right anybody using anybody using seem
对任何使用任何人的人似乎
you seem okay
你看起来还好
remembers what struts I know someone I
记得我认识的人
talked to someone earlier she's
跟她以前的人说话
legitimately there okay yeah yeah whoa
合理地有，是的，哇，哇
whoa before spring amuse Edith
哇，春天逗了伊迪丝
you know a lot of us were using yeah so
你知道我们很多人都在用
but the reason I'm asking is because we
但我问的原因是因为我们
actually do work with just about
实际上与
anything that you want to work with and
您想使用的任何东西，以及
it's kind of to get a feel for what's
有点感觉是什么
going on in the world Eclipse and STS
在世界各地进行的Eclipse和STS
are you know my favorite but there's
你知道我的最爱吗，但是
also the guys who like you know IntelliJ
也喜欢你的人知道IntelliJ
like this guy well you know I love
像这个家伙一样，你知道我爱
NetBeans it's I do and who uses NetBeans
我是NetBeans，使用NetBeans的人
here know what come on one of you does
在这里知道你们身上发生了什么
right and all kidding aside that was
对的，除了开玩笑
touched and really nice so they have
感动，真的很好，所以他们有
Auto completion for Spring Buddha never
自动完成春佛
they do so anyway I have a friend named
他们还是这样做，我有一个朋友叫
gear trainers gets yeah he gets at every
齿轮训练师得到了，他得到了每一个
time I make a crack about Nepean so say
一次我对Nepean有所了解
that Joanne why she start wearing some
乔安妮为什么她开始穿一些
code okay do that well you know into the
代码好吧，你知道吗
pic clinic one first yeah sure talk
图片诊所一个首先是肯定的谈话
about stateful so the pic clinic is kind
关于有状态，所以图片诊所是善良的
of a larger much larger application and
更大的应用程序
then we'll look at using them right
那么我们来看一下正确使用它们
spring boot from from zero to turnaround
spring boot 从零到周转
right we'll go to nothing to actually an
对，我们将一事无成
app that does a thing yeah make some
做某事的应用程序让一些
changes to it you'll see like you know
更改它，您将看到像您所知道的
what kind of stuff and then where you
什么样的东西，然后你在哪里
gonna go afterwards well with that
以后会顺利进行
application is it my favorite place ever
应用程序是我最喜欢的地方
I don't always test my code but when I
我并不总是测试我的代码，但是当我
do I test it in prod so we're actually
我要在产品中测试它，所以我们实际上是
going to go from nothing to pushing an
从无到有要
app to cloud foundry and then actually
应用程序到Cloud Foundry，然后实际
making some changes and you'll see it
进行一些更改，您会看到它
was really cool and we're also going
真的很酷，我们也要去
after this awkward like three-minute
经过三分钟的尴尬
pause while we wait for Cloud Foundry to
在我们等待Cloud Foundry暂停时暂停
actually the first time yeah the first
其实第一次是第一次
time the second time not so much yeah
第二次没有那么多时间
cuz there's no yeah it's fine so do you
因为没有，没关系，你呢
want let's see how this looks
想让我们看看它看起来如何
let's see how this because you know it's
让我们看看这是怎么回事，因为你知道
always kind of an iffy proposition when
总是有点虚假的命题
you go from desktop to a projector I can
您从台式机转到投影仪，我可以
make the code bigger to let's see it's
使代码更大，让我们看看
all pixelated man oh really
所有像素化的人哦，真的
if I do this I'm gonna know it's gonna
如果我这样做，我会知道它会
happen
发生
they're Clips yeah mark a token for you
他们是剪辑，是的，为您标记一个令牌
yes a peek all right awesome
是的，一看就好了
so let's see how this goes actually
所以让我们看看实际情况如何
first let's just kind of talk about like
首先，让我们来谈论一下
you know how to even get J alright so
你知道怎么让J好吧
it's an IDE plugin for convenience
这是一个IDE插件，为方便起见
purposes only so you just go to the
目的只是为了让你去
marketplace or the plug-in directory if
市场或插件目录（如果有）
you're using IntelliJ and get it from
您正在使用IntelliJ并从
there and then configurations like to
然后在那里配置
check boxes you know pick your app
您知道的复选框，选择您的应用
server and your app or just your app if
服务器和您的应用，或者仅在您的应用（如果
you have an app server it's kinda cool
你有一个应用服务器，这很酷
but let's just say that I want to start
但我们只想说我想开始
my application this is so hard to do on
我的应用程序很难做到
the screen okay
屏幕还好
I have Tomcat I also wildfly rang too
我有Tomcat我也有野蝇响了
but finally font small I know he's good
但是最后字体小我知道他很好
it's like better is that too big though
好像更好，但是太大了
it might be too big no it's okay I
可能太大了，不，我可以
couldn't stand an adult man next to the
无法忍受旁边的成年男子
San serif yeah so here see this is just
是San Serif是的，所以在这里看到这仅仅是
a layer because you can't actually see
一层，因为您实际上看不到
their thing alright so this is the pot
他们的事还好，所以这是锅
okay so this is the spring pack my cap
好吧，这是我的帽子的弹簧包
right so this is like a traditional like
对，所以这就像传统的一样
not boo you know MVC application where
不嘘你知道MVC应用程序在哪里
you can have stateful you know sessions
你可以有状态地知道会议
and you can do like the cool stuff and
而且您可以喜欢很酷的东西
so actually no it means the old one
所以实际上不，它意味着旧的
there's so much more control so cool so
有更多的控制权，很酷，所以
how do you remember pet clinic anybody
你怎么还记得宠物诊所的人
okay so pet clinic was a sample
好吧，宠物诊所是一个样本
application that was originally put
最初放置的应用程序
together in 2004 maybe five in response
一起在2004年也许有五个回应
to the j2ee at the time pet clinic and
到当时的宠物诊所去j2ee，以及
then the microsoft pet clinic these are
然后微软宠物诊所
sample apps the answer two different
示例应用答案有两个不同
architectures and so the spring pet
建筑等等春天的宠物
clinic had the cuter animals that's why
诊所里有可爱的动物，这就是为什么
it's the better one right and it's been
这是更好的一项权利，
kind of pushed along you know it's
有点像你知道的
actually it's actually crazy is like
实际上这是疯狂的，就像
every year I you know go on this quest
你知道我每年都去做这个任务
can I find a better or like
我可以找到更好的还是喜欢的
all-inclusive application that shows how
展示如何
to use a framework and the answers
使用框架和答案
always no like it never
永远不喜欢它，从来没有
I'm never able to find one that like it
我永远找不到喜欢的人
is it all satisfactory so like you know
一切都令人满意吗，就像你知道的那样
here we have our traditional application
在这里，我们有传统的应用程序
right we have the spring pack like up
对了，我们的弹簧包像
it's a full like MVC app and I'm running
这是一个完整的像MVC应用程序，我正在运行
on Tomcat with Eclipse and the idea is
在带有Eclipse的Tomcat上，想法是
you know ask if there's a clinic I
你知道问我有没有诊所
haven't seen in years
多年未见
yeah so like I just kind of want to say
是的，就像我只是想说
hi to all you guys right so let's let's
大家好，让我们开始吧
do this two g-packs right some change
做这两个g包对一些变化
the messages that properties file right
属性文件正确的消息
just how I had just hit save that works
就像我刚刚击中保存的方式一样
all right
好吧
and so you see here in the console we
所以您可以在控制台中看到
get these helpful little messages right
正确获取这些有用的小消息
Jerry will reloaded this bundle file
Jerry将重新加载该捆绑文件
message about properties and so we
有关属性的消息，所以我们
actually know how to integrate with like
真正知道如何与喜欢
the framework and see like you know this
框架，就像你知道的那样
file changed what can we do with that
文件更改了我们该怎么办
it's not spring internationalization
不是春天的国际化
exactly not just I mean one thing chains
不只是我的意思是一件事
a property file even right even when I
一个属性文件，即使我
write but to get the framework to
写但要得到框架
understand that exactly right and so we
了解完全正确，所以我们
can do that we can also you know change
可以做到，我们也可以知道改变
like jsps without having to do
像jsps一样，不必做
repackaging or anything so for example i
重新包装之类的东西，例如我
wanted to change the local that JSP
想更改本地的JSP
that's in okay this guy you know this is
没关系，这个家伙，你知道这是
a so this is a clinic so maybe want to
一个所以这是诊所，所以也许想
be more clear about what this link
更清楚这个链接是什么
actually we're kind of owners we have so
实际上我们是这样的所有者
I'll find pet owners hit save
我会找到宠物主人的
refresh now we have pet on our toe right
现在刷新，我们的脚趾上有宠物
so that stuff that you know probably
所以你可能知道的东西
might be able to do without Jerry ball
也许不用杰瑞球就能做到
and that's fine but what you can't do is
很好，但是你不能做的是
actually maintain state and application
实际维护状态和应用程序
and make code changes so what we're
并更改代码，所以我们
gonna do is put on some form validation
要去做一些形式验证
right so if I hit submit you see that
对，所以如果我点击提交，您会看到
all the fields are currently required in
当前所有字段均为必填项
this form okay but let's say that we go
这种形式还可以，但是我们可以说
to the class that actually is used to
到实际上用来
validate this
验证这个
jrgen so we have this valid a method
约尔根，所以我们有这个有效的方法
and then this not any method has a whole
然后这不是任何方法都有一个整体
bunch of if statements right if I turn
如果我转一堆if语句正确
in code like this I probably get in
在这样的代码中我可能会进入
trouble
麻烦
and I think a lot of you would as well
我想你们很多人也会
so what we're gonna do is refactor us a
所以我们要做的就是重构我们一个
little bit right so let's say for
有点正确，所以我们说
example II want to make our last name
例二想姓我们
and first name put them into a new like
然后把名字改成新的名字
name validation method so I'm just gonna
名称验证方法，所以我要
extract the method right okay hit enter
提取方法好吧，打回车
so now we have a new method call where
所以现在我们有一个新的方法调用
those used to be right and then later in
那些曾经是正确的，后来
the class they've actually changed the
他们实际上改变了班级
schema so now we have our new method and
模式，现在我们有了新方法
then you know maybe we want to change
那你知道也许我们想改变
the key that's being used for the first
第一个使用的密钥
name so I'll create a first name key and
名称，所以我将创建一个名字密钥，然后
add that to the message type properties
将其添加到消息类型属性
to okay so I hit save all I did was hit
没关系，所以我点击保存所有操作
save
救
we're relying on the incremental
我们依靠增量
compiler inside of Eclipse to keep out
Eclipse内的编译器保持隔离
of that for me but IntelliJ instead of
对我来说，但是IntelliJ而不是
save you would just hit control of nine
除非你控制九点
or something to compile that class I go
或一些我去上课的东西
to path link again hit refresh we see
到路径链接再次点击刷新，我们看到
here in the console that the class and
在控制台中，该类和
the bundle file both got reloaded right
捆绑文件都重新加载正确
and if I make that smaller go here our
如果我做的更小，请到这里
new keys in place right so I can also
新钥匙就位，所以我也可以
add some state right so let's say I want
添加一些状态，所以说我想要
to put in a phone number hit submit we
放入电话号码点击提交我们
actually now have a object in our
实际上现在我们有一个对象
session that has that owner right that
具有该所有者权利的会话
owner object I'm use this as a phone
所有者对象，我将其用作电话
number and economic other changes too
数量和经济其他变化
and we're going to keep that so let's
我们将保持这一点，让我们
say for example I want to change this to
例如说我想将其更改为
fail right so economic lastname optional
对不对，因此经济姓氏可选
hit save go back here hit refresh now
点击保存返回此处点击刷新
last names optional phone number still
姓氏可选电话号码仍然
there I've saved a one full day look at
在那里，我保存了整整一天的时间
this it's so helpful
这很有帮助
I didn't plan that at all seriously
我根本没有认真计划
high-five it's a high-five from David
高五，这是大卫的高五
yeah we also have little helpful
是的，我们也没有什么帮助
messages like you know you save so much
像您知道的消息，您可以节省很多
time ask for a raise stuff like that
时间要求加薪这样的东西
right and it's because we actually have
对，这是因为我们实际上有
people who have gotten raises because
得到加薪的人，因为
they're just like I was able to get all
他们就像我能够得到所有
my Sprint's done
我的Sprint完成了
more problems and everyone loves week
更多的问题，每个人都喜欢一周
right so we actually of people actually
对，所以我们实际上是
have a guy who got like direct bonus
有一个得到直接奖金的家伙
from a VP at a finance company because
来自一家金融公司的副总裁，因为
he was like yeah I did all this stuff I
他就像是的，我做了所有这些事情
didn't have to do any deploys and
无需进行任何部署，
they're like wow you are so awesome you
他们就像哇，你真棒
saved us from this problem
使我们免于这个问题
great I I think of Jerry was helping to
伟大的二世想到杰里
help serve humanity right the more the
帮助更多地服务于人类
faster we can reload code is enjoyable
我们可以更快地重新加载代码
but more or less likely we are to go to
但是我们或多或少会去
PHP and I think there's a direct
PHP，我认为这是直接的
correspondence between happiness and
幸福与
humanity and that move yeah I actually
人性，那举动是的，我实际上
got into an argument in a bar about this
在酒吧里对此争论不休
once because this guy's no way that like
曾经因为这个家伙绝不是那样
yeah no you know what no so this guy
是的，不，你不知道，所以这个家伙
basically said that because Java has too
基本上说，因为Java也有
much tooling around it right and there's
围绕它的很多工具，还有
all this like stuff like these build
所有这些都像这些东西
processes never have to you guys PHP is
进程永远不需要你们PHP
way better and it's just like well
更好，就像一样好
you're giving up a lot of stuff right we
您正在放弃很多东西，我们
can we can solve the tooling problem and
我们可以解决工具问题吗？
keep the superior runtime and everything
保持卓越的运行时和一切
else right so we're doing that but no
没错，所以我们正在这样做，但是没有
okay so far I've won like change stuff
好吧，到目前为止，我赢了喜欢改变的东西
that art exists in our project right but
该艺术存在于我们的项目中，但是
what if I want actually got a new class
如果我想上一堂新课怎么办
and it also modifies some spring config
并且还修改了一些spring配置
and making this new class actually do
并让这门新课真正开始
cool stuff right so have this my double
很酷的东西，所以这是我的两倍
beam right here it's a simple getter and
梁在这里，这是一个简单的吸气剂，
setter for a string well done yeah I
二传手做的很好，是的，我
think so so I may actually put on the
这么想，所以我实际上可以穿上
classpath cuz right now it's not okay
classpath cuz现在不行
see see it's pretty cool so I'm just
看到它很酷，所以我只是
gonna put this into my source in there
会把它放到我那里
okay so we have a that class now exists
好，所以我们现在有一个该类
it's now in my my standard packages I
现在在我的标准包装中
can also now go into the servlet
现在也可以进入servlet
you know and this is where a little spot
你知道，这是一个小地方
but I can actually add my new beam right
但实际上我可以添加新光束
here and alright found it okay so we're
在这里，还好吧，所以我们
gonna inject his erupt around into that
要把他的爆发注入周围
string and then we're gonna go into the
字符串，然后我们将进入
add owner form and we're gonna actually
添加所有者表格，我们实际上将
wire that beam first we can import it
先把那根线连接好，我们可以导入
and then we're gonna go and actually add
然后我们去实际添加
the wiring in we're gonna actually use
我们将实际使用的接线
it as well so when we call setup form
它也是如此，所以当我们调用设置表单时
we're gonna set the first name in that
我们将在其中设置名字
form to whatever spring in Jackson
形成到杰克逊的任何春天
that'd be okay so this is all cool I
没关系，这很酷，我
know this problem is showing you it's
知道这个问题向您显示
the marker now that matters intro is
现在重要的标志是
fine so now I can go home
好吧，现在我可以回家了
hit that forum and it works right yeah
打那个论坛，它是正确的
that's pretty cool right so we can see
那很酷，所以我们可以看到
that actually that we hooked in and we
实际上，我们迷上了我们
found like we need to reload the spring
发现像我们需要重新加载弹簧
mean definitions we add that in class
均值定义，我们在课堂上添加
you add any beam in the environment and
您在环境中添加任何光束，
then we also just do a quick refresh on
然后我们也可以快速刷新
some beans as well if we need to and we
如果需要的话，还有一些豆子，我们
didn't have to you know redeploy the app
不必知道重新部署应用程序
or rebuild it or anything I'm a fan
或重建它或任何我喜欢的东西
yeah it's pretty nifty I wish I had this
是的，这很漂亮我希望我有这个
before and so that's kind of cool you
之前，所以这很酷
can also like extend your configuration
也可以扩展您的配置
so if you are still using XML you can
因此，如果您仍在使用XML，则可以
just change your ports and we'll pick
只需更改您的端口，我们会选择
that up as well but do you want to move
以及，但你想移动
on to boot now do you think okay yeah it
马上启动，您认为好吗
still gonna kill this this is an
仍然会杀死这是一个
existing app and it's it's helpful to
现有的应用程序，这对
look at this stuff in the context of an
在一个背景下看这些东西
existing app because I think J Roble has
现有应用程序，因为我认为J Roble有
a lot of value for these large
这些巨大的价值
applications are out there if you're
如果您正在申请
trying to to go quickly and you're kind
尝试快速走，你很友善
of being buried under the weight of the
被埋在
startup for the app itself
应用本身的启动
it was absolutist right there's a lot of
是专制主义者，有很多
apps that were built in yesteryear and
过去构建的应用程序和
we can't escape that and there's a
我们无法逃脱，有一个
gravity these applications tend to have
这些应用程序倾向于具有重力
where new features get added in
在其中添加了新功能
but as that just seems like the easiest
但这似乎是最简单的
you know path of least resistance but
你知道阻力最小的路径，但是
it's also to appreciate that this is
也要意识到这是
something you can use when in front when
当你在前面时可以使用的东西
starting from from zero yeah you go to
从零开始，是的，
start that starting from start out to
从开始到开始
fingernail right so I do let's do this
正确的指甲，让我这样做
so I'm gonna go ahead and build a brand
所以我要去建立一个品牌
new application my same kind of typical
新应用程序与我相同
spring blue application how many of you
春天的蓝色应用你们有多少
well nevermind it's it's all meaningless
没关系，这都是毫无意义的
there's no internet what are we even
没有互联网，我们什至
doing what does it all mean
做这一切意味着什么
she was one just choose the one that
她只是选择一个
works yeah well here we are now we're
很好，在这里，我们现在，我们在
cooking
烹饪
oh I know this
哦，我知道这个
don't tell anyone yeah no one knows to
不要告诉任何人，是的，没人知道
know this you don't even know us cool ha
知道这个，你甚至都不知道我们很酷哈
ha you're that it works yes okay right
哈，你的意思是，可以，对吧
now so this is start that spring that I
现在，这是那个春天开始，我
know how many of you have been here or
知道你们中有多少人来过
see me see me talk about it anyone it's
看到我看到我谈论它的任何人
actually his homepage it's my favorite
实际上他的主页是我的最爱
place except for production right so
除了生产权以外的地方
this is an amazing place lots of good
这是一个很棒的好地方
stuff here if you get a chance you
如果有机会，这里的东西
should go it's kind of a woman cuz
应该去吧，有点像女人
you're going shopping so I'm just gonna
你要去购物，所以我要
go ahead and choose spring boot 1.3 I'm
继续并选择Spring Boot 1.3我是
gonna pick a jar as opposed to a dot
要选择一个罐子而不是一个点
waar or done eater right yes jars are
waar或吃完了的人，对，罐子是
good so in jars this is very much in
很好，所以放在罐子里
keeping with my my personal philosophy
符合我的个人哲学
of make jar not war so we have that year
使罐子不是战争，所以我们有那一年
we're gonna build a web application use
我们将建立一个Web应用程序使用
JPA
JPA
what else to want to try we need age to
还有什么想尝试的，我们还需要年龄
database we need actuator we need a
数据库，我们需要执行器，我们需要一个
template why not it's a web application
模板为什么不是Web应用程序
okay that should do for now I guess
好吧，现在应该做
well that work actually maybe that'll
好吧，那工作也许会
work
工作
so do we try that one that one I think
所以我们尝试那个我认为的那个
won't figure out yeah so one of the
不会知道是的，所以其中之一
things is because food is so like
事情是因为食物是如此
up-and-coming and cool and it's pivoting
崭露头角，令人着迷
such an awesome job of like writing new
像写新书这样的很棒的工作
code for all the time it's required to
在需要的所有时间进行编码
keep up so like if you're trying
跟上，如果你正在尝试
something and it doesn't work if you let
有些东西，如果你让它不起作用
us know will generally fix it pretty
我们知道通常可以很好地解决它
quickly but you know because we have
很快，但是你知道，因为我们有
such a crazy amount of all the
如此疯狂的数量
frameworks that we support a lot of
我们支持很多的框架
sometimes it is it is like use case
有时候就像用例
driven so yes that's a Toby's gonna work
开车，是的，那是托比的作品
with this knowing did you set it up yeah
知道了吗，您设置好了吗
just file open if I this is the one that
只是打开文件，如果我这是那个
we were using
我们正在使用
oh this one was it yeah okay open here
哦，这是吗，是的，可以在这里打开
we go how do you use this thing yeah
我们去你怎么用这个东西耶
okay okay so let's see here
好吧好吧，让我们看看这里
that's the open dialogue sorry
那是公开对话，对不起
oh yeah it's figuring things out
哦，是的
getting dependencies no well okay
得到依赖不好
actually we should go back and just
其实我们应该回去
choose 1.25 then let's see how far it's
选择1.25，然后看看它有多远
gone no I'm not even sure okay whatever
走了不，我什至不知道还好
was good at that
擅长于
yeah so what I'm going to try and do is
是的，所以我要尝试做的是
go as far as I can without a reload some
尽我所能，无需重新加载一些
things require me loads right if you
事情需要我正确的负载，如果你
change things on the class path you need
改变您需要的课堂路径上的东西
to you need you to restart even with
您是否需要重新启动
zero turnaround right and spring boot
零周转权和弹簧启动
offers a model where sometimes the very
提供了一个模型，有时
presence of something in the class path
类路径中存在某种东西
means that you have to take action
意味着你必须采取行动
you're going to be prompted to correct
您将被提示更正
the state of the application before it
申请之前的状态
will start up correctly so as far as I
就我而言将正确启动
know the one thing where we might run
知道我们可以在哪里跑一件事
into a road bump right now is that we
现在是路障
have on this class path here spring boot
在这个班上有 spring boot
starter time leaf accessibility
初学者时间叶可访问性
not this one it's just um peripherals do
不是这个，只是外围设备
you see accessibility thank you so I
您看到可访问性，谢谢，所以我
have a spring boots starter Titan II if
如果有 spring boot 起动器泰坦二世
on the classpath this is a templating
在类路径上，这是一个模板
engine there are many such templating
引擎有很多这样的模板
engines that are supported by spring
Spring 支持的发动机
boot including GUI server pages there's
引导包括GUI服务器页面
tie and leaf there's velocity free mark
领带和叶子上有自由速度标记
or whatever they're gonna check for the
或他们要检查的
presence of a template and when they
模板的存在以及何时
when it starts up its gonna bulk at the
当它开始时会在
absence of that template so we need to
缺少该模板，因此我们需要
satisfy it by going to get hub that
通过获得枢纽来满足它
conjure move for micro services I know
想到我知道的微服务转移
computer
电脑
taking this HTML command a and then I'm
采取这个HTML命令，然后
gonna create a new template here and
要在这里创建一个新模板，
that would be the only thing that will
那将是唯一的事情
will we need to do before we can restart
我们需要做些什么才能重新启动
okay so we'll revisit it later but if we
好的，我们稍后再重访，但是如果我们
don't have that it'll fail so one of the
没有它会失败，所以其中之一
coolest things about food is that yeah
关于食物最酷的事情是
it actually does add new dependencies as
它实际上确实添加了新的依赖项
you have code that used they need them
您有使用他们需要它们的代码
unfortunately like with jarred well you
不幸的是，就像你受了伤
can't actually add and remove like
不能像这样实际添加和删除
dependencies from your app right so like
来自应用程序的依赖关系，就像
for example we work with log4j but you
例如，我们使用log4j，但是您
can't change which version of log4j are
无法更改哪个版本的log4j
you using while the apps running right
您在应用正常运行时使用
they can't they can't leak modify your
他们不能，他们不能泄漏修改您的
palm and have that work but some of what
掌心工作，但有一些
boot does is actually like hey you have
开机确实就像嘿，你有
this code in your app and I'm starting
此代码在您的应用中，我开始
up so I'm gonna pull this thing out
起来，所以我要把这个东西拉出来
which is cool but that's one of the
这很酷，但这是其中之一
caveats
注意事项
I'm a fan so here we go I'm gonna run
我是粉丝，所以我们要走了
with J rebel now did I have to do
现在与J反叛者有关系吗
anything to do want to show the people
有什么事想向人们展示
anything that needs to be done in
需要做的任何事情
IntelliJ since were visiting yes so now
IntelliJ自从访问以来就这样
that we were in intelligent world let's
我们在智能世界中，让我们
go actually all the things I said check
实际去我所说的所有内容
this box right so now we have this
这个盒子，所以现在我们有了这个
jerilyn abled on the module and then
jerilyn启用了该模块，然后
just make this go away and then when you
只是让它消失，然后当你
run
跑
yeah yes
是的，是的
good cool so then you see like you're
很酷，所以你会发现你就像
you you can always tell whether gerbils
你总是可以告诉你沙鼠
like actually installed or not because
喜欢实际安装或不，因为
of that banner when you use load with
当您使用load时，该横幅的
the console up put your information like
控制台将您的信息
yeah the boot stuff is awesome the boot
是的，启动的东西很棒
banner is better I think we can only
横幅更好，我认为我们只能
look you're a skier it's better I get it
看起来你是一名滑雪者，我会更好
okay have we talked about this basket
好，我们谈论过这个篮子了吗
rec this ask Carol work is beautiful
REC This Ask Carol工作很美
people they ask all the time can we
他们一直问的人可以
change it can we remove it and of course
改变它我们可以删除它，当然
you can but that's what I usually start
你可以，但这就是我通常开始的事情
flipping tables that's a bad idea folks
翻转桌子是个坏主意
why would you want to remove this a
你为什么要删除这个
scale record we have two people on the
规模记录我们有两个人
on a spring team who are doctors PhDs in
在一个春季团队中，他们是
their previous lives that concern
他们以前关心的生活
themselves with the fairy stars of the
自己与神仙的星星
blow us and it makes me happy to imagine
打击我们，这让我很高兴想象
that at one point they got to get have
在某一点上，他们必须拥有
issue that said we need good ass get
说我们需要好屁股的问题
work and they did it delivered its
工作，他们做到了
beauty right now you could replace that
美丽，现在您可以替换它
but you know could you do a better job I
但是你知道你能做得更好吗
couldn't no this just be clear I mean I
不能不，这只是很清楚我的意思是我
want to remind you of this tale of
想让您想起这个故事
Icarus who's arrogant conceit and trying
傲慢自负和尝试的伊卡洛斯
to trying to craft wings and fly him to
尝试制作翅膀并飞向
the Sun eventually brought him low could
太阳最终使他低落
you bit do better maybe but I doubt it
你可能做得更好，但我对此表示怀疑
so we just leave it know at this point
所以我们现在就让它知道
I'd also like to take issue with
我也想对
intelligent I've been picking a NetBeans
我一直在选择NetBeans
it's fair that I you know let's just I
我很公平，你知道我就是
just want to have this out I just want
我只想拥有这个
to say I think that we should start a a
说我认为我们应该开始
petition and and get them to remove this
请愿书，让他们删除
radik at his feature now this is the
萝卜在他的功能，现在这是
dumbest thing that they've ran it so why
他们已经运行了最愚蠢的东西，为什么
are you using at the time to write a
您当时在使用写一个
thing that removes the banner from booth
从展位上取下横幅的东西
what oh why why when they're in the
哦，为什么为什么当他们在
middle of making all of their like
使他们都喜欢的中间
awesome autocomplete stuff someone also
很棒的自动完成功能，也有人
said let's spend 10 minutes doing this -
说让我们花10分钟来做这件事-
well we have like okay if you use this
好吧，如果您使用此功能，我们会喜欢
bring out application builder at
在以下位置带出应用程序构建器
election there's actually an a
选举实际上有一个
programmatic API
程序化API
let's remove it but we didn't expect any
让我们删除它，但是我们没想到
would ever call it that's just not
会称之为那不是
tonight kosher so anyway whatever
今晚洁净，无论如何
okay don't care so it's running it's
好吧，不在乎，它正在运行
fine okay so the application is fine
很好，所以应用程序很好
right we got the application up and
好的，我们启动了应用程序，
running I suppose the first thing we
运行我想我们第一件事
need
需要
do is create a entity of some sort right
做的是创建某种形式的实体
so can you all read that is that a
所以你们都可以读到
little too small I'm gonna make Adams
太小了，我要去做亚当斯
font inseparably large and then I won't
字体不可分割的大，然后我不会
notice because I don't really use in
注意，因为我并没有真正使用
touch often and then like six months
经常触摸，然后像六个月
from now when I open it again I'll be
从现在开始当我再次打开它
really surprised and then I'll send Josh
真的很惊讶，然后我将派乔什
a message on skype was like making fun
Skype上的消息就像在取笑
of him like you jerk does it everything
像你这个混蛋那样做的一切
anyway yeah
反正
yeah yeah it's okay we'll make about
是的，我们会解决的
that's that's pretty okay
那没关系
so class reservation always the same
所以班级预订总是一样的
domain because we don't care about the
域，因为我们不在乎
domain and we just care about the speed
域，我们只关心速度
and the velocity so I'm gonna create a
和速度，所以我要创建一个
JP entity this is just straight JP a
JP实体，这只是笔直的JP一个
it's gonna have a primary key here that
这里要有一个主键
ID at generated value it's gonna have
具有生成价值的ID
that's no sorry I'm using Adams keyboard
对不起，我使用亚当斯键盘
here and I'm not feeling at home okay
在这里，我感觉不舒服
it's gonna have get it to kind of have
它一定会拥有它
getters well shift answers
吸气剂转移答案
yeah so the way Joshua's right now my
是的，约书亚现在的样子
keyboard so I often last week we were
键盘，所以我上周经常
both in Norway for another show and
都在挪威参加另一个节目
someone brought over with our computer
有人带走了我们的计算机
to me like hey help me figure out what's
对我就像嘿，帮我弄清楚是什么
wrong with Nigeria we'll install and the
尼日利亚的错误，我们将安装和
guy has a Norwegian keyboard and I'm
家伙有挪威键盘，而我
really good
真的很好
I don't understand why it's so hard to
我不明白为什么这么难
write a four slash like why don't hit
写一个四斜杠，例如为什么不打
three keys link literally control in
三个键直接按字面控制
okay generate Gators there go in
好吧，生成鳄鱼进入
constructor control again again okay
构造函数再次控制好吗
to stream and keep them I like while
流并保持它们我喜欢
he's doing this like the app still
他仍然像应用程序一样这样做
running so like if you actually had you
就像你真的有你一样
know something you're actually doing
知道你在做什么
useful with it then it would still be
有用的话它仍然会
out while he's doing all this cool stuff
在他做所有这些很酷的事情时
so I'm gonna create a command line
所以我要创建一个命令行
runner that'll will that work that
跑步者将工作
should work right yeah oh yeah you
应该正确工作是的，哦，是的，你
should do mmm what's that oh yeah please
应该做mmm那是什么哦，是的
update yeah okay cool so basically we
更新，是的，很酷，所以基本上我们
last year we came out with a new core
去年我们推出了一个新的核心
for Jerell that does some more stuff
为杰瑞尔做更多的事情
like you can now actually do like the
就像你现在可以像
interfaces and super classes and
接口和超类以及
everything else
其他一切
so actually what we should do just cut
所以实际上我们应该做的只是削减
this or yeah it's commented out it comes
这个或是的，它被注释掉了
out the things that we did that are
我们所做的事情是
meaningful yeah okay cool so we're gonna
有意义，是的，很酷，我们要
do while you were here should done this
你在这里的时候应该做的
so if you ever get a message in your IDE
因此，如果您在IDE中收到消息
saying you should try the new core this
说你应该尝试新的核心
is what it means
是什么意思
basically we keep the old core around
基本上我们保留了旧的核心
just in case someone actually needs it
万一有人真的需要它
for some reason but the new core lets
由于某种原因，但新的核心让
you do a lot of cool new stuff like so
你会做很多很酷的新东西
did I have to resent for that yeah like
我是否必须为此而讨厌
basically the new core lets you add
基本上，新核心可以让您添加
remove implement interfaces and
删除机具接口并
superclass is an actual migrated fields
超类是实际迁移的字段
like if you extract out of your
就像你从自己身上抽出来一样
superclass it'll actually migrate the
超类实际上将迁移
field and then save the state in the
字段，然后将状态保存在
instance so it's pretty cool
实例，所以很酷
but yes changing a job agent does
但是是的，更换工作代理确实可以
require you to restart your jadianna so
要求您重启贾迪安娜，所以
but what's important is Josh commented
但重要的是乔希评论
out that annotation and he will then
删除该注释，然后他将
uncomment it and it'll work
取消注释，它将起作用
splendidly are we good okay we're up and
很棒，我们很好吗，我们起来了，
running here we go so interface
在这里运行，我们去界面
reservation repository this is a spring
预订库，这是春天
data repository it's gonna use entities
数据库将使用实体
of type reservation with a primary key
具有主键的类型保留
of type long I'm gonna use JPA here I'll
我将在这里使用JPA的类型
bring in the command line runner again
再次引入命令行运行程序
okay at the bean the command line
在bean的命令行上还可以
runners a spring boot interface that
引导一个弹簧启动界面
gets called when the application starts
在应用程序启动时被调用
up it's actually really cool how it
真的很酷
works - like it's a it's a pretty cool
可行-就像它一样，非常酷
way of just like seating seating some
就像就座
information into your app and the kind
信息进入您的应用程序和种类
of stuff I'm Fanning are so good for you
我正在范宁做的事情对你很好
know that and I'm gonna raise this list
知道了，我要提出这个清单
Peter Brian there we are
彼得·布莱恩（Peter Brian）
that or ejects it's also like you know
或弹出它，就像你知道
terrible those working on like the land
那些像土地一样工作的人
of stuff in Java 8 and streams and
Java 8和流中的内容
everything else
其他一切
Josh's Landers are gonna work perfectly
乔什的着陆器会完美地工作
so if I just do build just command if9
所以如果我只是建立命令if9
on yours in yeah well I see results yeah
是的，在你的身上，我看到了结果，是的
so then when Jarrell sees that the
所以当Jarrell看到
classes got compiled it actually shows
类得到编译，实际上显示
you messages and then in the new core it
您的消息，然后在新的核心
pre loads them into the JVM before you
在您将其预加载到JVM中之前
use them in the old core it's more of a
在旧的核心中使用它们更像是
lazy lazy reloading so as you use code
懒惰懒惰重装，以便您使用代码
we actually pull the new ones in then
我们实际上是在拉新的
then pull the new version so I'm gonna
然后拉新版本，所以我要
make this a rest repository that should
使它成为应该
work too right yeah sure
工作太正确了，确定
okay so command F Knight again and I
好吧，再次命令F Knight和我
should be able to go to localhost
应该可以去本地主机
reservations
预约
to be Jesus one before
成为耶稣前一个
worst-case we could arrest a controller
最坏的情况下，我们可能会逮捕一名管制员
yeah that is fine class reservation rest
是的，这是上等的舱位休息
controller that on a wired private
有线专用控制器
reservation repository and request
预订库和请求
mapping reservations great here we go
地图预订很棒，我们去了
now return this don't reservation
现在返回这个不要保留
repository I'd find all and command if
我会找到所有存储库并命令是否
nine
九
did it do it looks like it might have
它做了它看起来好像有吗
there we go yeah so there's the data
我们去了，所以有数据
that was a REST API a very simple spring
那是REST API的一个非常简单的春天
MVC component right obviously this
MVC组件显然是这个
wouldn't be much of a demo without some
没有一些就不会是一个演示
sort of an MVC component as well so I'll
也是MVC组件，所以我将
actually build a regular spring MVC
实际建立一个常规的春季MVC
controller like this as opposed to a
像这样的控制器，而不是
rest controller Reservations
rest controller 预订
MVC controller on wired private
有线专用MVC控制器
reservation repository called enter and
预订存储库称为enter和
I'm going to create an endpoint that'll
我将创建一个端点
have a URL that I would never actually
有一个我从未真正使用过的URL
use in production this is a demo I just
在生产中使用这只是一个演示
want to underscore that here now this is
要强调的是，现在这是
a hypothetical okay something
假设的好事
nonsensical that will never ever happen
愚蠢的，永远不会发生
in the real world reservations at PHP no
在现实世界中保留在PHP no
page model and I'll return this
页面模型，我将返回
reservation repository I'd find all nope
预订资料库我会找到所有
I'm gonna return model that at attribute
我要归还属性的模型
sorry reservations new line for space
对不起，预订新的空间行
and posterity return the string
后代返回字符串
reservations and that of course will
保留，当然
resolve ultimately it'll be resolved via
最终将通过以下方式解决
a a vewy solver which is a spring these
一个春天的求解器，这些
spring MVC ism is a heuristic that will
Spring MVC ism是一种启发式
look on the classpath for a template
在类路径上查找模板
it'll plug in the string reservations
它将插入字符串保留
into that and heuristic in this case the
在这种情况下启发式
auto configuration for time leaf will
自动配置时间片将
automatically be sent to look for the
自动发送以查找
template and source main resources
模板和源主要资源
templates like that okay so if that's up
这样的模板就可以了，如果可以的话
and running command f9 or of course you
并运行命令f9或您
would call we have this template here
会叫我们这里有这个模板
right that's where we kept it and that
对，就是我们保留它的地方
was we had originally to make timely
是我们本来必须及时做出来的
Pappy when we actually started the app
实际启动应用程序时的Pappy
in the first place exactly every time
恰好每次
leaves does the scanning it freaks out
叶子会吓跑它的扫描
if it's like there's no templates so you
如果没有模板，那么您
have something that worked that works
有一些有效的方法
well I've got you know we can see that
好吧，我知道你可以看到
with spring boot there's still a value
spring boot 仍然有价值
in having a the J Roble support there
在那里得到J Roble的支持
because is for the common components for
因为是用于
the kinds of things
各种各样的东西
wouldn't want to do this is really
真的不想这样做
really powerful and even if you don't
真的很强大，即使您没有
even if you're just saving a little bit
即使您只是存一点钱
for the for the restarts it helps it
对于重新启动它有帮助
adds up you know a death of death by a
加起来，你知道一个人的死
thousand cuts however we're really
千切，但我们真的
really gives nice especially for me
真的对我特别好
because I spend a lot of time in
因为我花很多时间在
production because I love production is
生产，因为我爱生产是
the ability to actually move this to the
实际将其移至
move this application yeah to a cloud
将此应用程序移动到云中
and then sort of get that working so can
然后可以使它正常工作
you you want to take them there so yeah
你想带他们去那里
you know one of the things that you know
你知道其中一件事
you've probably heard a lot about this
您可能已经听说过很多
week and the last few months and maybe
一周以及最后几个月，也许
even the year from pivotal microservices
即使是关键微服务的一年
are really awesome so you know if you
真的很棒，所以你知道你是否
wanna run microservices we've actually
想运行我们实际上已经使用过的微服务
partnered with pivotal to get Jarrell as
与关键合作伙伴将Jarrell任命为
part of the build pack so if you use
构建包的一部分，因此，如果您使用
terrible and then you go to actually
糟透了，然后你去
deploy an app in cloud foundry we
我们在Cloud Foundry中部署应用
actually do the server-side config for
实际为服务器端配置
you in cloud foundry and you can just
您在Cloud Foundry中，您可以
code the same way we are now without
编码方式与我们现在没有的方式相同
having to restage your apps and say
必须重新整理您的应用并说
what's really cool it's a bill tank atom
真正酷的是票据罐原子
well you see when using cloud foundry he
好吧，您看到使用Cloud Foundry时，他
basically picked what what kind of app
基本上选择了什么样的应用程序
you want and here what you're gonna use
你想要的，这里你会用的
Java because we're you know we're cool
Java，因为我们知道您很酷
we're Java devs like that and so the
我们就是这样的Java开发人员，所以
idea is that I'm actually going to take
想法是我实际上要
you through the experience of taking
通过您的经历
this application and then pushing it to
该应用程序，然后将其推送到
a new app in cloud foundry and then we
云铸造中的一个新应用程序，然后我们
can show that stuff actually works the
可以表明这些东西确实有效
way that we want it so the build pack is
我们想要它的方式，因此构建包是
the bit that actually looks at the
实际看到的
incoming code from the from the client
来自客户端的传入代码
whether it's a Java dot jar or Java dot
是Java点jar还是Java点
war or a PHP application or a rails
战争或PHP应用程序或Rails
application or nodejs application or
应用程序或nodejs应用程序或
whatever and it detects what kind of
不管它检测到哪种
artifact it is and it detects the
它是伪像，它检测到
environments that it's going to need so
它需要的环境
for example if it's a Java Dyer it'll
例如，如果它是Java Dyer，它将
it'll lay down the jdk to lay down a
它会放下jdk放下
cost path or lay down you know the path
成本的路径或放下你知道的路径
variable correctly on all those stuff
在所有这些东西上正确地变量
it'll set up everything you need if it's
它会设置您需要的一切
a don't war it'll stand up Tomcat and
不要战争，它将使Tomcat站起来，
then deploy inside that for you so and
然后在里面为您部署
it doesn't based on detection so it
它不是基于检测的，所以
actually looks at with the applications
实际上看与应用程序
on so what he's gonna do is now retrofit
这样他现在要做的就是翻新
occasion that we just built yeah and
有时候我们只是建造了
teach it how to how to cloud so we're
教它如何去云，所以我们
gonna have to deploy it but then we can
将不得不部署它，但是我们可以
make changes right so I'm gonna stop it
进行正确的更改，以便我停止
because now we don't care about it
因为现在我们不在乎
raining luckily I stopped that he says
幸运的是，我下雨了，他说
he clicks the wrong button yes exactly
他点击了错误的按钮
so then carefully there you go yeah so
所以然后仔细地去那里是的
now you see this and you look like cloud
现在你看到了，看起来像云
thing right here click on that yeah it's
在这里的东西，是的，是的
a cloud the rocket oh it's adorable it
乌云火箭哦可爱
is right it's pretty durable and
是的，它非常耐用，
cinnamon here to our preferences and go
肉桂在这里，我们的喜好去
to the gerbil section then we go to
到沙鼠部分，然后我们去
actually know how I do that that's good
其实知道我是怎么做到的
yes no this guy cool so I enabled
是的，这个家伙很酷，所以我启用了
remoting right here in Jarrell and what
在Jarrell进行远程处理以及什么
you do is we actually use the servlet
您要做的是我们实际上使用了servlet
context of the deployed application and
部署的应用程序的上下文以及
that's how we get the files into cloud
这就是我们将文件放入云的方式
foundry so you don't have to worry let's
铸造，所以您不必担心，让我们
say for example you have a VM or
例如说您有一个VM或
something you know in your company we'll
您在公司中知道的一些信息
do the same thing there - so there's no
在那里做同样的事情-所以没有
concern about firewalls so what I'm
担心防火墙，所以我是
gonna show you is really cool with cloud
会告诉你云真的很棒
foundry and for using spring food micro
铸造和使用春季食品微
services this works pretty well but if
服务，效果很好，但是如果
for example you are in a different
例如你在不同的地方
paradigm where you have like a VM
像虚拟机一样的范式
somewhere or you've docker or something
某个地方或您有泊坞窗之类的东西
this will work the same way so I'm going
这将以相同的方式工作，所以我要
to I don't have an app yet so I don't
我还没有应用，所以我没有
have a URL but I'm just gonna do that
有一个URL，但我只是要这样做
this is your thing right yeah cool
这是你的事对，很酷
so as you need to put it to Cloud
因此您需要将其放入云端
Foundry I'm sure you've seen this once
铸造厂，我确定您已经看过一次
or twice this week yeah maybe you guys
这个星期两次或两次，是的，你们
have seen Cloud Foundry so what I want
看过Cloud Foundry所以我想要什么
to show you is this is really important
告诉你这真的很重要
is this file rebel - remote this is the
这个文件是反叛的-远程这是
magic sauce that makes Java that makes
使Java产生的神奇酱
the build pack ad Jebel and do awesome
构建包广告Jebel，表现出色
stuff so what we're gonna do is to build
东西，所以我们要做的是建立
my app
我的应用
it's getting a little bit but it's been
有一点点但是已经
really cool and worthwhile cool and I'm
真的很酷，很值得，我
gonna end up with a jar hmm we have
最终会得到一个罐子，嗯，我们有
tests you why'd you write tests right
测试您为什么要编写正确的测试
wait wait what just ran to us it's a
等一下，刚才跑给我们的是
default test it just starts the
默认测试它只是启动
application up and down
上下应用
I know okay so I'm your machine that
我知道，所以我是你的机器
start up and down was 11 seconds it's 11
启动和下降是11秒，这是11
seconds that J roll saves us yeah the
J翻滚拯救我们的秒数，是的
screen what's that copy this jar here we
屏幕是什么，在这里复制这个罐子，我们
go okay all right happy so now I'm gonna
好的，好吧，现在我要
actually create a new app um somebody I
实际创建一个新的应用，我
push I do control you know clear screen
推我控制你知道清晰的屏幕
what do you want call this uh jr. boob s
你想怎么称呼这个……布布
to G X sure peas all right okay that's
向GX确认豌豆好吧，那是
the path so yeah the first parameter
路径，所以是第一个参数
specifies the timeout yeah because it's
指定超时是的，因为它是
gonna wire up a Java agent that needs to
将连接一个需要
be there so you'll notice that it it's
在那里，所以您会注意到它是
just a wee bit slower at startup but of
刚启动时有点慢，但是
course you more than make up for over
当然，您不仅仅可以弥补
the something resource and the idea is
一些资源和想法是
also if you are in the code true
如果您在代码中也是如此
microservices architecture and you're
微服务架构，您
working on like five services at once
一次处理五项服务
that's cool you just push them all and
太酷了，您只需将它们全部推开，
get them started and then you'll add you
让他们开始，然后您将添加您
know the URLs for each of them into your
知道他们每个人的网址
ID and you can be to work on all of them
ID，您可以对所有这些进行处理
as if they were native on your local
就像他们是您本地人一样
machine so this'll take a few minutes in
机器，所以这需要几分钟
the meantime since we are trying to very
同时，由于我们正在努力
very clearly stall here anybody have any
很明显，这里有人失速
questions so dev tools is a thing that's
问题，因此开发工具是一回事
in spring boot 1.3 dev tools just tosses
在 spring boot 1.3开发工具只是折腾
out the application context so Java
排除应用程序上下文，因此Java
itself has some overhead as well so
本身也有一些开销
that's one of the things you're gaining
那是你获得的东西之一
by using something like dev tools or
通过使用开发工具之类的工具或
zero turnaround but as we don't you lose
零周转，但因为我们不，你输了
all your state so dev tools just tosses
您所有的状态，所以开发工具只是扔
the application context it's fairly fast
应用程序上下文，它相当快
for modern like spring boot applications
适用于现代之类的 spring boot 应用
to
至
especially microservices to just throw
尤其是微服务
away the context and then start again if
离开上下文，然后重新开始
your state is in the in the in the
您的状态在中
session then you're going to lose that
会议，那么你会失去那个
but again hopefully you're not doing too
但还是希望你不要这样做
much with the session you know but
你知道的会议很多，但是
what's also cool is like for example
例如，什么也很酷
let's say you're using the you know
假设您使用的是您知道的
in-memory database and you have you know
内存数据库，您知道
JPA or something in your service and you
JPA或您服务中的某些内容，您
have you know data in your memory
您是否知道内存中的数据
database if you make changes to your you
数据库，如果您对自己进行更改
know JPI stuff like your entities or
知道JPI之类的东西，例如您的实体或
whatever will actually pick that up and
任何实际上会捡起来的东西
you know do the right thing in the in
你知道在做正确的事
memory database so that your fields
内存数据库，以便您的字段
actually persist the way you expect them
真正坚持您期望他们的方式
to and so you don't trash that either
到，所以你也不会垃圾
right so you've been don't have session
对，所以您一直没有参加会议
state and you just have some database
状态，你只有一些数据库
state you're using for your app you
说明您正在为您的应用使用
won't lose that either and so it's
也不会失去它，所以它是
pretty cool
很酷
does that help okay other ones yes sir
这样可以帮助其他人吗
ma'am sorry I'm sorry justify yourself
对不起，对不起，为自己辩护
I'm gonna look next time I'm really
我下次再看
sorry
抱歉
well as you add so when you're making
以及添加时，
changes to the single page app on the
更改为单页应用
client side there's a couple parts that
客户端有几个部分
actually if you're just doing regular
实际上，如果您只是定期做
HTML and you're not doing a build
HTML并且您没有进行构建
pipeline like going to whatever you can
管道就像去到你所能
probably get away with without durable
可能没有持久就摆脱
right because you can just you can
对，因为你可以
actually reload those templates and
实际重新加载这些模板，
artifacts in the class on the on the
类上的神器
client and you can tell even regular
客户，你甚至可以告诉定期
eclipse or IntelliJ just to load the
Eclipse或IntelliJ只是为了加载
JavaScript if you're tying it into a
JavaScript，如果您将其绑定到
built pipeline of course gonna want to
建好的管道当然要
run that step and then you'll have
运行该步骤，然后您将拥有
updated content on the to be served
要投放的更新内容
artifacts you know HTML pages so that's
您知道HTML页面的工件，因此
still that's pretty normal but if you're
还是很正常的，但是如果你是
adding rest services if reading business
阅读业务时增加休息服务
logic on the backend that can become a
后端的逻辑可以变成
gating factor of especially for a large
选通因数尤其对于大
application so if you have a lot of
应用程序，所以如果你有很多
services in the back and you've got a
后面的服务，您有一个
lot of state there it's gonna be nice to
那里的很多州会很好
not have to trash that state every
不必每次都浪费该状态
single time you want to add a new
一次您想添加一个新
service at endpoint also like with with
端点上的服务也与with
jeroboam everything is being done
jeroboam一切都在做
server-side so like if you hit
服务器端就像打
refreshing your browser to pull in some
刷新浏览器以拉入一些
new things you know if you had some
你知道一些新事物
JavaScript or your thrashing the
JavaScript或您的
JavaScript runtime environment when you
您的JavaScript运行时环境
do that so that would be a concern yeah
这样做，那将是一个问题，是的
yeah so you can change things with at
是的，所以您可以在
like post construct you can change
像后期构造，您可以更改
method signatures - absolutely so you
方法签名-绝对让您
can change signatures schemas of the
可以更改
classic you want to add or move you can
您想添加或移动的经典
do you can you know new statics you can
你能知道新的静力学吗
t change things in the stack initializer
更改堆栈初始化程序中的内容
of the class like I said there's a state
就像我说的那种状态
migration from super classes apply it so
从超级类迁移适用
it's worked so well now how long did it
现在已经工作了多久了
take again remember the alternative to
再次记住其他的
this is the alternative to this is
这是替代方案是
standing up a server right so again this
正确地站立服务器，这又
is a market improvement over not having
是因为没有市场改善
a cloud however if you're trying to do
云，但是，如果您尝试这样做
development there's some configuration
开发有一些配置
issue or some weirdness that's only
只是一些问题或怪异
happening the cloud environment it can
可以在云环境中发生
be very handy to be able to push changes
非常方便能够推动更改
from the client cool all right so we can
从客户端很酷，所以我们可以
open a new one your fancy oh my gosh
打开一个新的你喜欢的哦我的天哪
Tara boots as to GX yep see if apps
塔拉（Tara）启动GX Yeep，看看是否有应用
today oh cool so do this course this was
今天哦，很酷，所以这门课程是
actually the thing you did there making
实际上你在那里做的事情
your cool so our apps now in cloud
太酷了，因此我们的应用程序现在已经在云端
foundry and I can take this URL I have
铸造厂，我可以使用这个网址
promised and put this into IntelliJ go
承诺并将其放入IntelliJ go
back to that screen add our application
回到该屏幕添加我们的应用程序
apply okay now when I make a change and
现在，当我进行更改时，请立即申请
I hit the ctrl F 9 it'll actually
我按了Ctrl F 9，实际上
synchronize that change to cloud foundry
将更改同步到Cloud Foundry
and then we'll just hit refresh and
然后我们点击刷新，
Chrome and you'll see that it works
Chrome，您会发现它可以正常工作
Council in debug yeah actually you can
理事会在调试是的，实际上你可以
if you instead or two basically you can
如果您改为一两个基本上可以
hook it with the debugger options that
将其与调试器选项挂钩
you can have breakpoints and stuff and
你可以有断点和东西，
they'll work it's pretty nifty
他们会工作的，这很漂亮
so what do I try where's the MVC
那我该怎么试MVC在哪里
controller I think that's the most
控制器，我认为这是最
obvious let's start with something
显而易见，让我们开始
simple like an HTML page yeah sure so go
像HTML页面一样简单，可以
back to the template time if template
回到模板时间，如果模板
make that change yeah so again we're
做出改变，是的，所以我们再次
dealing with an application running on a
处理在
cloud in some other state now
现在处于其他状态
yeah well where is it is I no idea I
是的，那是哪里，我不知道
wasn't used to think yeah actually might
不习惯认为是的
be near here
在这附近
Virginia remind us not that far but
弗吉尼亚提醒我们不远，但
still in theory it could be yeah so
从理论上讲仍然是这样
reservation at spring 2015 carry and f9
于2015年春季预定，携带和F9
no I need you're coming up that may be
不，我需要你来这可能是
but so we see we have this message here
但是，我们看到这里有此消息
uczt synchronized right there so you see
uczt在那里同步了，所以你看到了
the secret spouse to the server and so
服务器的秘密配偶等等
before you know reservations on PHP yeah
在您了解对PHP的保留之前
right timely is kicking in and doing
适时适时开展工作
stuff
东西
hello computer computer box
你好电脑电脑盒
ah oopsies sorry
哎呀对不起
what is happening huh this makes me sad
发生什么了，这让我伤心
a little bit I'm not sure what's going
有点我不确定会发生什么
on I think I'm not sure if it's the
我想我不确定这是否是
Internet's heat or something else this
互联网的热度或其他
is fine so I can actually also do this
很好，所以我实际上也可以这样做
let's see if this is anything useful
让我们看看这是否有用
go to the code meantime what's the MVC
同时转到代码是什么MVC
controller yeah do we do well yeah it
管制员，我们做得很好吗
looks right yeah are you sure you're
看起来不错，是吗，确定要
using enough force enough gusto you
用足够的力量来吸引你
broken
破碎
log back just throwing chunks yeah of
重新登录只是扔大块耶
course this work just yeah it's ago they
当然，这项工作只是在他们之前
did whatever mmm that's weird
做了什么奇怪的事
I blame the demo gods okay let's get
我责怪演示神，好吧，让我们开始吧
away from that far away far far away
远离那遥远的地方
mr. Evans thank yours let's get a new
先生。埃文斯（Evans）谢谢您让我们得到一个新的
controller yeah sure
控制器是的
that's fine never mind you sure okay so
没关系，您确定可以，所以
fine that failed crashed and burned
失败失败并烧毁的罚款
horribly miserably and sadly um but it
可怕而可悲的是
is I don't think a lot of us spend a lot
我不认为我们很多人会花很多钱吗
of time I don't know maybe you got maybe
时间我不知道也许你得到了
you all do but as far as I've seen a lot
你们都做，但据我所知
of his stuff spent a lot of time doing
他的东西花了很多时间做
server-side HTML so hopefully that's not
服务器端HTML，所以希望不是
something that's too often or maybe
太过频繁或也许
you're just doing a static file so this
你只是在做一个静态文件，所以这
is a rest endpoint so I'll say hi sorry
是休息的终点，所以我打个招呼对不起
like that came out of 9 dad should work
像是从9爸爸出来的
dude what just happened all of the magic
花花公子，发生了所有的魔术
that was working just stopped mmm
那正在工作只是停止了mmm
okay so picked it up it's synchronize
好吧，所以拿起它来同步
diet hmm let's try this
饮食嗯，让我们试试这个
I have an idea literally no idea I do I
我真的有一个主意
really do we just did this like
真的，我们只是这样做了吗
literally right that was the one part I
从字面上看，那是我的一部分
was a little worried about so we just
有点担心，所以我们只是
did it and now not so much
做了，现在没有那么多
okay could be good
好吧可能很好
what Sunday the Java agent is after all
毕竟Java代理是星期几
keeping its own dispatch table of
保持自己的调度表
everything in the virtual machine it's a
虚拟机中的所有内容
little bit of indirection between the
之间的一点间接
actual tables and the code that's
实际的表和代码
running on top of it something up the
在它上面运行的东西
class letter basically we instrument
班级信件我们基本上是乐器
like all the app codes so we can make it
像所有应用程序代码一样，我们可以做到
be right over by us so it's possible
就在我们身边，所以有可能
that I forgot to add the memory flag
我忘记添加内存标志
this time and that's the problem
这次就是问题
oh you I know well anyway if that's it
哦，无论如何我都知道
that would make sense cuz you need to
这会很有意义，因为您需要
keep the memory somewhere right in the
将内存保持在正确的位置
region usually I keep my memory and
通常我会保持记忆和
memory yeah
记忆是的
you can also follow along with the logs
您还可以遵循日志
and you can see what's happening during
你可以看到发生了什么
the build pack initialization didn't so
构建包初始化不是这样
happens that there isn't a mention that
碰巧没有提到
that remote file basically if that
该远程文件基本上是
remote file exists then the build pack
远程文件存在，则构建包
has a script that goes and pulls down
有一个可以删除的脚本
the durable jar and then adds a server
耐用的jar，然后添加服务器
side for you see you sit around that
一边看到你坐在那边
remember remote what do I wanted to do
记得遥远我想做什么
and it's gonna do cool stuff it's
它会做一些很酷的事情
working
工作中
yes no I have my memory so we're good
是的，不，我有记忆，所以我们很好
this is obviously way more than I
这显然比我要多
actually need to gauge this and absurd
实际需要衡量和荒谬
them out but I figure this way we're
他们出来，但我想这样我们
absolutely safe safe is good safe is
绝对安全安全就是安全
good quick and safe yes exactly I think
好快速又安全是，我想
that makes ago I took longer to start up
这使得我花了更长的时间来启动
to this I'm happy about that
为此，我对此感到高兴
Laurel container it's true
月桂树的容器是真的
so any other questions that I can say
所以我能说的其他问题
while we're waiting for this to come
当我们等待这件事来的时候
back up yes no we just production
备份是否我们只是生产
doesn't mean like actual production
并不意味着像实际生产
production like environment so you can
像生产环境一样可以
actually have parody never never in
实际上有模仿永远不会
production yeah yeah please don't do
生产是的，请不要
that yes exactly so he says production
是的，所以他说生产
he needs like the cloud
他需要像云一样
so that a new can if you get it working
这样一来，新的罐头就可以工作了
in your local one your then CF push to
在您本地的那个然后CF推到
the real thing you know it's working
你知道它正在起作用的真实事物
yeah but you can iterate and so on
是的，但是您可以迭代等等
quickly
很快
yeah so that yeah sorry so if that was
是的，所以是的，抱歉，如果那是
not scary
不吓人
I'm sorry I can
对不起，我可以
well I mean it's a secret right so so
好吧，我的意思是这是一个秘密，所以
the Casey's asking basically what we do
凯西基本上在问我们该怎么做
and so we basically I said we rewrite
所以我们基本上说我们重写了
the classes with instrumentation so that
带有仪器的类，以便
we can make them rewritable and do
我们可以使它们可擦写并执行
whatever we want to do with them so the
无论我们想与他们做什么，所以
idea here being that instead of having
这里的想法是，而不是拥有
you know the way permanent right so
你知道永久的方式吧
happens can't see this work yes
碰巧看不​​到这项工作是
please
请
better than before but not really
比以前更好，但不是真的
reservation so let's just see if the
预订，所以让我们看看
page without the change works son of a
页面没有更改工作的儿子
motherless goat the other logs
无母山羊其他原木
well that's it isn't it a reskin tour I
好吧，那不是我的换肤之旅
think so maybe yeah I don't know I
认为是吧，也许我不知道我
logged back those are doing anything
重新登录那些正在做什么
here this is real weird thing and of
这是真正的奇怪的事情，
course it's only happening I know yeah
当然只有我知道
when we're on stage yeah we can do have
当我们在舞台上，是的，我们可以
an idea what do this well worst case
一个想法，这怎么办最坏的情况
yeah we're fat fingering something or
是的，我们正在发指或
missing something right pretty obvious
缺少一些显而易见的东西
well we will use the app that I
好吧，我们将使用我
definitely know worked before we just
绝对知道我们之前工作过
did it blue needs to her yeah there's
蓝色对她来说需要吗？
always this guy I it was a happy spot
总是这个家伙，我很高兴
here I do continuous integration and my
我在这里进行持续整合，
continuous integration always goes to
持续集成始终
plan fund rate so I can test it that way
计划基金利率，这样我就可以进行测试
what I'm doing
我在做什么
micro-services I do a lot of my
微服务我做了很多
development locally however for a lot of
但是在当地发展
us there's gonna have bigger
我们会有更大的
applications and these applications tend
应用程序，这些应用程序往往
to have corner of cases that you only
拥有只属于你的情况
discover when you move from one
发现何时离开
environment to another hopefully
希望有另一个环境
continuous integration on earth SAP but
在SAP上持续集成，但
it can be very slow to to fix it so you
修复起来可能很慢，所以您
want this to work
希望这个工作
yes okay it's not rich oh yeah but I
是的，它并不丰富哦，是的，但是我
used upstairs and we just bowed if it
在楼上用过，如果我们鞠躬的话
doesn't work yeah it doesn't work if
不起作用是的，如果不起作用
you're not us and on stage that is a
你不是我们，在舞台上
magic trick yeah if we have time to
魔术，是的，如果我们有时间
actually debug it figure out what that
实际调试它找出什么
log back errors than we did how much
重新记录错误比我们做的要多
patience of this working class oh well
这个工人阶级的耐心哦
yeah happens if there are any quick
是的，如果有任何快速发生
other questions in the meantime but
同时还有其他问题
otherwise I want to thank you very much
不然我要非常感谢你
yeah stick around to see if it works I
是的，坚持走下去看看我是否可行
want to see it work I just do
想看看我刚刚做的工作
yeah that's why it's a matter of pride
是的，这就是为什么这是一个骄傲的问题
it'll work
会的
yeah so any other questions that's up
是的，所以还有其他问题
yep
是的
a speck J's interesting some of it works
斑点J的有趣之处
some of a dozen depends on what you're
十几个取决于你是什么
doing
在做
exhibits like compile-time type stuff
像编译时一样的东西
then you know no because you'd have to
那你就不知道，因为你必须
basically call your you have to call
基本上打电话给你，你必须打电话
whatever actually runs that again but if
任何实际再次运行，但如果
you're doing load time we think it
你在做加载时间，我们认为
should be okay
应该还可以
yes so how do we get access basically we
是的，所以我们基本上如何获得访问权限
are good friends with the people at
在这里与人们成为好朋友
pivotal and so when you have that file
关键的，因此当您拥有该文件时
it brings in our agent on the server
它在服务器上引入了我们的代理
side and there's also a special Java
方面，还有一个特殊的Java
option that gets added and what that
添加的选项以及那
Java option does is it says enable
Java选项确实说启用
remote act and that let me see we create
远程行为，让我看到我们创造的
a context like a special hidden contacts
像特殊的隐藏联系人这样的上下文
that we then use to send files over HTTP
然后我们用来通过HTTP发送文件
and so in Cloud Foundry instance and
在Cloud Foundry实例中
bases a little temp directory we have a
基于一个临时目录，我们有一个
copy of the you know compiled version of
您知道的编译版本的副本
your application we swap that in there
您的应用程序，我们在那里交换
and basically treat it like it's a local
基本上把它当成当地人对待
install so we don't have any access to
安装，因此我们无权访问
your accounts or anything special or
您的帐户或其他特殊内容，或
cool like weird like that as low just a
酷得像怪异的一样低，只有一个
matter of we use HTTP to send files and
我们使用HTTP发送文件并
then we you know do gerbil
那我们知道沙鼠吗
reloading on them as if they were a
重新加载它们，就好像它们是
local yeah and this is how we're able to
是的，这就是我们能够做到的
avoid having a deal with like firewalls
避免处理类似防火墙的问题
and stuff in the enterprise environments
和企业环境中的东西
right because we're always using HTTP
对，因为我们一直在使用HTTP
and they can't block that yeah that's
他们不能阻止那是的
what you're using for your app in the
您在应用中使用的是什么
first place right so make sure which
排在第一位，因此请确保
file is it which module let's just make
文件是哪个模块让我们制作
sure that we do this first to make sure
确保我们首先执行此操作以确保
they have the right gentleman of the
他们有正确的绅士
project oh it's that one yeah like let's
项目哦，就像我们这样
make sure that we have this is the right
确保我们有这个权利
URL
网址
oh that's important no but which code
哦，那很重要，不，但是哪个代码
we're working the wrong code no this is
我们正在使用错误的代码，这不是
the one that we that worked upstairs
我们在楼上工作的那个
okay this is the one we're at this point
好的，这是我们现在要使用的那个
where to showing a change that actually
在哪里显示实际上的变化
does a thing
做某事
okay let's do it right so here okay so
好吧，让我们做正确的事情，所以在这里好吧，所以
yes we have a controller that actually
是的，我们有一个控制器，实际上
does something now and the app works
现在执行某项操作，该应用即可正常运行
good
好
Oh oh that hurt me so bad it works
哦哦，那太伤我了
you're not touching it again we're not
你不会再碰它，我们不会
it's good it's fine you can go get some
很好，你可以去拿点东西
lunch yeah it's amazing just he's gonna
午餐，是的，只是他要
put that in github and then I'm gonna
把它放在github上，然后我要
tweet it and star it and say this is the
鸣叫并加注星标，然后说这是
thing that got me yeah and you will know
是的让我知道的事情，你会知道
what to copy when you're trying to do it
尝试复制时要复制的内容
like no you're not there's some things
就像不，你不存在某些东西
that you know I don't know why log back
您知道我不知道为什么重新登录
is having issues but you can see we
有问题，但你可以看到我们
synchronized that they to the URL with
与他们同步到URL
the context and the file was transferred
上下文和文件已传输
successfully
成功地
no no repackaging after that wasn't the
没有没有重新包装，那不是
missing boot version perhaps I might
缺少启动版本，也许我可能
have been might have been this I'm using
一直可能是我正在使用的这个
a milestone versus that yeah oh that
与那个里程碑，是的，哦，那
makes me so sad let me see was it a
让我很难过，让我看看是不是
timely file that's one then no no but we
及时的文件，然后是不，但我们
can add a new controller yeah like yeah
可以添加一个新的控制器，像是
we're gonna do that just yeah just for
我们要做的只是
posterity
后人
no it's compiling then it's gonna
不，它正在编译，然后它将
transfer and my conference Wi-Fi that's
传输和我的会议Wi-Fi
fine conference Wi-Fi is always fast no
精美的会议Wi-Fi总是很快没有
not that one
不是那个
come on it's maybe two slash huh
来吧，也许是两个斜线吧
if we do this or not yeah
如果我们这样做还是不可以
Durr
杜尔
yeah it's loaded yeah you just you okay
是的，它已经加载了，是的，你就好了
you have to wait for Wi-Fi to do the
您必须等待Wi-Fi进行
right thing but that does work it's
正确的事情，但这确实有效
infinitely faster when you're connected
连线时无限快
to Wi-Fi yeah thank you so much yeah
Wi-Fi是的，非常感谢你
if you have questions we'll be happy to
如果您有任何疑问，我们将很乐意
take them have a good lunch you have a
带他们吃一顿美味的午餐
great show go say hi
很棒的节目去打个招呼
you
您